Jorgensen, Keir Collection of Video Recordings about Sweatshops 6274 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Keir Jorgensen Collection of Video Recordings about Sweatshops
1994- 2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jorgensen, Keir
6274 AV
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
Many of these are video recordings of segments of TV news magazines (60 Minutes, Dateline NBC, Hard Copy, etc.). There are two copies of some of the enclosed tapes.
7997586
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Sweatshops; Jorgensen, Keir
7997586
- The Hidden Face of globalization, 1 (Box 1)
- Nike (Prime Time, 6/9/1974), 2 (Box 1)
- Nike CEO at National Press Club - May, 1998, 3 (Box 1)
- The Carpet Slaves: Stolen Children of India (Cinemax, March 26, 2001 Reel Life Series) by Kate Blewett and Brian Woods, 4 (Box 1)
- Nike in Indonesia (CBS Street Stories, 7/2/1993), 5 (Box 1)
- Behind the Seams - December 11, 1994, 6 (Box 1)
- Child Labor "Rights, Wrongs, PBS, 7/25/1996", 7 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Kathy Lee Gifford, Biography, E&E, 12/16/1996; Toy Story - Dateline NBC, 12/17/1996
- Mickey Mouse Goes to Haiti: Walt Disney and the Science of Exploitation, 8 (Box 1)
- McNeil Lehrer Newshour (Katie Quan) - 8/17/1995, 9 (Box 1)
- Dita Inda Sari (Indonesia), BBC hardtalk, Sept. 1999, 10 (Box 1)
- Jeff Fiedler on china (CNBC, 5/25/1994), 11 (Box 1)
- Frank Gifford at Sweatshop, CNN (5/23/1996); Living Wills, etc. (Channel 13, PBS); Child Labor, ABC News w/Peter Jennings, 6/11/1996, 12 (Box 1)
- Chinese Military - NBC Dateline, May 10, 1994, 13 (Box 1)
- Toy Story: Indonesia and China Sweatshops - 12/1996, 14 (Box 1)
- Football (60 Minutes), 15 (Box 1)
- ESPN "Made in Vietnam"; April 2, 1998, 16 (Box 1)
- Eye to Eye with C. Chung Pakistan Child Labor (CBS, April 6, 1995), 17 (Box 1)
- CBS Evening News - Segment on Saipan With Jack Shenkman of ACTWU, 18 (Box 1)
- The Real Fashion Slaves (Burmese migrant garment workers in Mae Sot, Thailand), Norwegian Church Aid, November 2003, 19 (Box 1)
- Blood, Sweat, and Toys (Kader fire in Thailand; China) American Journal, 1995, 20 (Box 1)
- 60 Minutes: China-Slave Labor; WRC Ch4 11/14/1991 NBC Nightly News: Products from Chinese Prison Labor Camps, 21 (Box 1)
- Rights and Wrongs - PBS (4/25/1996) -- Illegal Chinese immigration NYC Sweatshop, 22 (Box 1)
- Donahue - 10/2/1995 on Sweatshops, 1 (Box 2)
- Nike, Inc. in Indonesia (CBS Street Stories, July 2, 1993), 2 (Box 2)
- Consumer goods imports from plants run by Chinese Military (NBC Dateline, May 10, 1994), 3 (Box 2)
- Bangladesh Apparel Industry (NBC Dateline, 12/22/1992), 4 (Box 2)
- Consumer Goods Imports from plants run by Chinese Military (NBC Dateline, May 10, 1994), 5 (Box 2)
- Nike in Vietnam - 48 Hours (CBS) 10/17/1996; Sweatshops (part 2) - Dateline NBC - 10/20/1996, 6 (Box 2)
- ABC Primetime Live - 10/15/1997 - Executed Prisoners Organs in China, 7 (Box 2)
- Nicaragua Sweatshops (Hard Copy, Nov. 1997), 8 (Box 2)
- Wal-Mart (Dateline NBC); business Insiders (with Jeff Fiedler) (CNBC), 9 (Box 2)
- Something to Hide, 10 (Box 2)
- Globalization and Human Rights - October 29, 1998 (PBS), 11 (Box 2)
- Child Labor in Pakistan (Eye to Eye, CBS, 4/6/1995), 12 (Box 2)
- Worker Rights in Asia (CNBC, 5/24/1994), 13 (Box 2)
- Child Labor in Pakistan, on Eye to Eye with Connie Chung (CBS, April 6, 1995), 14 (Box 2)
- Nike, Inc. in Indonesia (CBS Street Stories) - July 2, 1993, 15 (Box 2)
- Of Human Bondage: Modern Day Slavery - ABC News Turning Point - 8/31/1994, 16 (Box 2)
- Saipan (CBS News ) - 9/16/1992, 17 (Box 2)
- Child Labor in Pakistan (Canadian youth visits Pakistan re: Iqbal Masih's Death) - 60 Minutes (CBS) - April 21, 1996, 18 (Box 2)
- Designer Sweatshops - ABC News - Feb. 2, 1996, 19 (Box 2)
- 60 Minutes - 9/27/1996 -- Nightline, 9/29/1992 -- Donahue Show, 10/6/1992, 20 (Box 2)
- Just Do It (Nike, Inc.) - Prime Time, ABC - June 9, 1994, 21 (Box 2)